Contact

vrromero1969@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vicki-romero-salinas-20aa855a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

ICU

Healthcare

Inpatient

Vicki Romero Salinas

RN, BSN, MBA, CCRN, NE-BC

Texas City, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Intensive Care, Medical-Surgical, Medication Administration, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.) focused in Health/Health Care Administration/Management from University of Texas at Tyler and NE-BC.

Experience

UTMB

22 years 8 months

Clinical Operations Administrator July 2013 - Present (6 years 11 months)

R.N.

October 1997 - Present (22 years 8 months)

Surgical/Trauma/Transplant ICU

HCA

RN

March 2009 - 2010 (1 year)

ICU PRN

Tenet Healthcare

RN

November 2006 - July 2007 (9 months)

SICU

Education

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston

BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2000 - 2001)

College of the Mainland
ADN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1996 - 1998)

University of Texas at Tyler

Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.), Health/Health Care

Administration/Management · (2013 - 2015)